It's going to be one hell of a family reunion.
Petals on the Wind is a tv movie, romance, thriller
film directed by Karen Moncrieff.
This sequel to Flowers in the Attic picks up 10 years after Cathy,
Chris and Carrie managed to escape Foxworth Hall.
Corrine Winslow, played by Heather Graham.
Cathy Dollanganger, played by Rose McIver.
Christopher Dollanganger Jr., played by Wyatt Nash.
Carrie Dollanganger, played by Bailey De Young.
Dr. Reeves, played by Nick Searcy.
Bart Winslow, played by Dylan Bruce.
Petals on the Wind is a 2014 Lifetime movie sequel to the 2014 adaptation Flowers in the Attic,
starring Heather Graham, Rose McIver, Wyatt Nash, Bailey Buntain and Ellen Burstyn.
It is based on V.
Andrews' 1980 novel of the same name, the second
novel on the Dollanganger series.
The film follows the surviving Dollanganger children—Cathy, Chris
and Carrie—ten years after escaping the attic.
Despite attempting to move on with their lives, after multiple failed attempts and
tragedies occur, Cathy decides it is time to take revenge on her mother.
Lifetime first announced the film shortly before
Flowers in the Attic was released.
The network announced on the premiere of the movie the developing of the following books of the
Dollanganger series, If There Be Thorns and Seeds of Yesterday, both of which aired in 2015.
The film received a positive response from critics.
The tone is emotional and intense.